[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はしります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "走ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とびます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "跳びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のぼります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "登ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "振ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もぐります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "潜ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "押します"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たたきます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "叩きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ころびます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "転びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'なげます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "投げます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もちあげます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持ち上げます"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふりむきます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "振り向きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さかだちます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "逆立ちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぎゃく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "逆"
    }
]